Guide to the Edwin Montefiore Borchard Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Biographical Material and Memorabilia, 1920-1945; Series VI; 10" (2 boxes)
  - Stamp collecting correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 147, Folder 1380-1381)
  - Stamp collecting correspondence, 1940-1948 (Box 148, Folder 1382)
  - New Haven Orchestra Association, 1936-1938 (Box 148, Folder 1383-1388)
  - Income tax, 1940-1943 (Box 148, Folder 1389)
  - Life insurance, 1927 (Box 148, Folder 1390)
- Additional Material, 1938-1955, undated; Accession 1995-M-015; 75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  Addition inventory by Carol King 1994 Sep
  Received from: Yale Law School. 1994 Jul 20
  - Correspondence, 1942-1947, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-13)
  - Subject files
    - Criminal law/evidence, 1938. 1952-1955, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Muslim law, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - National Foreign Trade Council, Inc., Foreign Property-Holders Protective Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Patent law, 1942-1945, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Shansi Province, North China, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - "Tobacco Case", 1940 November (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Fragments, miscellaneous, 1942-1943, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)